dialog-semiconductor.com 2016-11-28

# Privacy Policy | Dialog Semiconductor

## 16 December 2013

Dialog Semiconductor PLC and its affiliates (Dialog, We, Us) adheres to the Privacy Policy, Cookie Policy and Legal Notices listed on this website [www.dialog-semiconductor.com](http://www.dialog-semiconductor.com/), which may be updated from time to time, regarding its collection, use and disclosure of personal and non-personal information collected through its website (the Website). By visiting our Website you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.

For the purposes of the UK Data protection Act 1998, Dialog is a data controller.

## Collection of Non-Personal Information

When you visit our Website our server automatically records information including but not limited to your domain, IP address, and the date, time and duration of your visit. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information, but rather the device that is being used to view our Website.

## Use of Non-Personal Information

We only use your non-personal information to see how people are accessing our Website and to help us better understand how it could be improved. We also use browser type, operating system, and page visits for statistical analysis of the Website' usage and navigation trends.

## Collection of Personal Information

You may provide personal information by filling in forms on our Website or by corresponding with us by phone, e-mail or otherwise. This includes information you provide when registering for an activity or service on our Website or when reporting a problem with the Website. The information you give us may include your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, employer, and a personal description.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small file that can be placed on your device's hard drive or on a website server. Cookies do not retrieve information about you stored on your device and do not corrupt or damage your device or its files. Most browsers automatically collect cookies but you do not have to accept a cookie, and you can in fact modify your browser so that it will not accept cookies. For more information about cookies including how to set your internet browser to reject cookies please go to[ _  www.allaboutcookies.org_](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

By continuing to use our Website, you agree to our use of cookies, according to the Cookie Policy, Privacy Policy and Legal Notices described on this website, www.dialog-semiconductor.com (the Website).

Different types of cookies are used for different purposes on our Website, these are known as: strictly necessary cookies, performance cookies, and functionality cookies. Some cookies may be provided by an external third party to provide additional functionality to our Website and these are included below.

#### Strictly necessary cookies

These are cookies that are essential to fulfil an action requested by you, such as identifying you as being logged in. If you prevent these cookies by adjusting your browser settings we cannot guarantee how our Website will perform during your visit.

#### Performance cookies

These are cookies used to improve our Website, for example for analytics that let us see how our Website is being used and where to make improvements. These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our Website. The information is collected in an anonymous form and includes the number of visitors, where visitors have come from to the Websites and the pages they visited.

#### Functionality cookies

These cookies enhance the performance and functionality of our Website, often as a result of something you’re doing as a user. For instance, we may personalise our content for you or remember your preferences.

#### Managing and Deleting Cookies

If you want to manage cookies, you can do so from your browser. You can find out how to do this by going to the help menu in your browser. Please see [_www.allaboutcookies.org_](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) for further information.

## Use and Disclosure of Personal Information

We maintain personal information for statistical purposes to improve our Website for users' needs, to offer and provide the services you request, to administer the Website, and to correspond with users.

We will not give or sell this information to third parties other than to assist us in providing information or services to you or to manage and improve the Website. We may share your personal information to third parties if we, or substantially all of our or the relevant affiliated company's assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by us about our users will be one of the transferred assets. We will also respond to legal requests for information where required by law to do so.

## Access to Personal Information stored on the Dialog Servers

You can modify or delete your personal information at any time. To do so, please contact your local Dialog office.

## Marketing emails

We may use your profile to communicate with you over e-mail provided you have. In addition, we may communicate with you over email in relation to the services on our Website. If you wish us to discontinue sending e-mails to you, we will terminate this within a reasonable period of time of receipt of your request.

## Security

We use up-to-date data storage and security techniques to protect your personal information from unauthorised access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorised modification or unlawful destruction or accidental loss.

## External Links

The Website may contain links to third party sites. Since Dialog does not control nor is responsible for the privacy practices of those websites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of these third party sites. This policy applies solely to personal information collected by our Websites.

## Your rights

You have the right to apply for a copy of the information we hold about you (for which a small administration fee may be charged) and to have any inaccurate information about you corrected.

## Contact information

If you have any questions in relation to this policy please contact your local Dialog office.
